Dominic J Mitchell

1-401-440-3243

dominic.joseph.mitchell.2018@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dominic-j-mitchell https://github.com/DominicJosephMitchell

Energetic & dynamic Full Stack Web Developer, Specializing in Front End Web Design. A business professional enthusiastic about Tech while constantly learning, and stretching the borders of my mind. I decided to continue my education to increase and advance my Tech knowledge and career. Graduate of (IEL) Institute – of – Entrepreneurship & Leadership, and Rhode Coders Web Development, and currently enrolled in (GA) General Assembly. With 30 years experience in Management, Leadership, Construction & eight years Technology skills.

Employment History

Web Design & Developer Fellow	GA – General Assembly	10/2018-present				
*Twelve week web development immersive program (600hrs plus)						
Advanced Support Center Eng I	Cox Communications	01/2013-06/2018				
*Team Lead&Trainer. Tester New Deployments. Procedure development, Set(Metrics).						
App Specialist – III Lead/Trainer	Up-Source	01/2012-12/2012				
*Level III Lead & Rep Trainer		_				
Consultant/Tech- Tier I, II	TMC	11/2010-01/2012				
*Establish/Direct/ Increase Profit Yearly.						
Founder / Entrepreneur	Mitchell Construction Inc	04/2004-11/2010				
*Risk bearing, organizing, and innovation.	Planning, organizing, leading, and controlling					

Education

Institute – of – Entrepreneurship & Leadership		
*HTML – CSS – JavaScript	Web Design & Deployment	
New Horizons Computer Learning Center		2011
*A+, Net+, Sec+, MCP&MCDST	Network Support Technician Certificate	
Community College of Rhode Island		2003
*Associates in Arts Degree		

⁻⁻⁻⁻⁻⁻⁻

Technical Skills

HMTL	CSS	JavaScript	Handlebars	Ajax	Ruby-on-Rails	Ruby
MongoDB	SQL	PM/BA	Leadership	Git-Hub	Management	Node.JS
React	Bash	Mongoose	Networking	Scrum/Agile	Wire-frame	API
Express	AWS	SQL	Bootstrap	SASS	jquery	json

Web Development Projects

- * **Tic Tac Toe:** A custom front-end JavaScript game engine which connects with a third-party API. Users sign-up/in with an email address to create an account.
- *Bucket List: HTML/CSS/Javascript/Leaflet (map)/AJAX/MongoDB/Mongoose and Express.
- *Trails: HTML/CSS/React//MongoDB/Mongoose, and Express.
- * Vacations: HTML/CSS multi-page user experience designed photo album.
- * Family Tree: HTML/CSS, and JavaScript ancestry database; users can sign-up/in with an email to create account.